ghananewslink.com 2010-04-24

# Privacy

Ghananewslink and its advertisers are committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Collection of personally identifiable information for memberships

Unless you register yourself Ghananewslink does not collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your email adddress, name, age, etc. To register yourself is optional. You can access most of the content of Ghananewslinkanonymously without registering yourself.

You must be 18 years or older before you can register yourself.

Your personally identifiable information is not sold to third parties.

Your personally identifiable information will be used to facilitate the communication between you and other members of Ghananewslink. You can determine yourself how if and how much personal information you want to share with the other visitors of Ghananewslink.

Collection of non-personally identifiable information

Ghananewslink does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the ip-address you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). This information is used to improve the website by - for example - analyzing which pages are popular and which pages need to be improved.The collected information is not sold to third-parties.

Usage of cookies by Ghananewslink

Ghananewslinkuses cookies to store information about the country and city from which you are surfing. This information is used to customise the website - content as well as advertisements - according to your geo-graphical location.

Ghananewslink uses cookies to remember you screenname when commenting on news articles and when joining the chatroom. Without these cookies you would need to re-type your screenname all the time.

Ghananewslink uses a cookie for the Say It Loud forum to determine whether you are a registered user. Without this cookie it will not be possible to automatically give you the priviliges of a registered user.

In all cases you can stop this usage of cookies by Ghananewslink by disabling cookies in your browser. In the help section of your browser you will also find information about how to remove existing cookies from Ghananewslink from your computer.

In general you can use Ghananewslinkwithout cookies although it might reduce the user-friendliness of the website.  
Usage of cookies by Advertisers

Ghananewslinkruns advertisements from various renowned advertising networks, such as Valueclick Media, Google and Adconion. Their usage of cookies is governed by the individual privacy policy of the advertising network in question.

A good resource to learn more about your consumer privacy in relation to these advertising networks is the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). On this website you can opt out from Behavioral Advertising for all the advertising networks which are member of the NAI.
